A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Hugh Morrow, Series 21 FA242
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files, 1960-1974; 1; 20.4 Cubic Feet 50 document boxes
  - Human Rights, "Pictorial History of the Black American", 1969 (Box 24, Folder 254)
  - "H" Miscellaneous, 1962-1973 (Box 24, Folder 255)
  - Impeachment (Richard Nixon), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 256)
  - Indians (Native Americans, New York State), 1971 (Box 24, Folder 257)
  - Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 258)
  - Insurance, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 259)
  - Insurance, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 260)
  - Insurance, Automobile, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 261)
  - Insurance, Automobile, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 262)
  - Insurance, Automobile, "Automobile Insurance-For What Benefit" Report, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 263)
  - Invitations, Miscellaneous, (Correspondence and Policy), 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 264)
  - Invitations, Miscellaneous, (Correspondence and Policy), 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 265)
  - Invitations, Miscellaneous, (Correspondence and Policy), 1965-1969 (Box 25, Folder 266)
  - Invitations, Miscellaneous, (Correspondence and Policy), 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 267)
  - Invitations, Miscellaneous, (Correspondence and Policy), 1960-1962 (Box 25, Folder 268)
  - Invitations, Correspondence Related to Past Invitations, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 269)
  - "I" Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 270)
  - Javits, Jacob, Senator, 1963-1972 (Box 26, Folder 271)
  - Javits, Jacob, Senator, 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 272)
  - Jennings, Tom, (Public Relations and Speechwriter), 1970-1974 (Box 26, Folder 273)
  - Johnpoll, Leona, (State Study Commission for NYC-Housing), 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 274)
  - Judges, Appointments, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 275)
  - "J" Miscellaneous, 1963 1974 (Box 26, Folder 276)
  - Keating, Kenneth B. Senator, 1959-1963 (Box 26, Folder 277)
  - King, Reverend Martin Luther, Address at New York State Civil War Centennial Commission, 1962 September 12 (Box 26, Folder 278)
  - Kline, Charlie, (Public Relations), 1900 1964 (Box 26, Folder 279)
  - Kraig, Bonnie, (Ch'u Silk Manuscript, China), 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 280)
  - "K" Miscellaneous, 1962-1971 (Box 26, Folder 281)
  - Labor, Miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 282)
  - Labor, Miscellaneous, 1965-1969 (Box 26, Folder 283)
  - Labor, Miscellaneous, 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 284)
  - Labor, (Labor Day Statement, Nelson A. Rockefeller), 1962 September 1 (Box 27, Folder 285)
  - Labor, NABS, Jobs, "Jobs for Hard-Core Unemployed", 1969 (Box 27, Folder 286)
  - Latin America, (Follow-up to Latin America Report), 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 287)
  - Latin America, (Follow-up to Latin America Report), 1969-1972 (Box 27, Folder 288)
  - Law Enforcement, (Attica: McKay Commission), 1972 April 15 (Box 27, Folder 289)
  - Law Enforcement, (Attica: McKay Commission, Background Memos), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 290)
  - Law Enforcement, (Attica: McKay Commission, Background Memos), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 291)
  - Law Enforcement, (Attica, Miscellaneous), 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 292)
  - Law Enforcement, (Attica, Miscellaneous), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 293)
  - Law Enforcement, (Attica, Miscellaneous), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 294)
  - Law Enforcement, (Court Reform), 1973 (Box 28, Folder 295)
  - Law Enforcement, (General), 1962-1973 (Box 28, Folder 296)
  - Law Enforcement, (Prison Reform, Hugh Jones Report), 1973 (Box 28, Folder 297)
  - Law Enforcement, (Prison Reform, Hugh Jones Report), 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 298)
  - Lefkowitz, Louis J. (Attorney General), 1961-1967 (Box 28, Folder 299)
  - Legislature, New York State, (Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1960-1973 (Box 28, Folder 300)
  - Leonard, Frank, (Washington DC), 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 301)
  - Levine, Bernie, (Speech Transcriber), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 302)
  - Life-skills School for the Handicapped Children, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 303)
  - Lindsey, John V. (See also Campaign Files NYC), 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 304)
  - Lindsey, John V. (See also Campaign Files NYC), 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 305)
  - Liquor Control, (Drinking Age, Etc), 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 306)
  - Liquor Control, (Drinking Age, Etc), 1964 (Box 29, Folder 307)
  - Lomas, Stanley, Inc. (Product Promotion), 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 308)
  - Lottery, New York State, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 309)
  - Lubell, Sam, (United Feature Syndicate, Inc.), 1963-1973 (Box 29, Folder 310)
  - "L" Miscellaneous, 1961-1972 (Box 29, Folder 311)
  - "Managing the News" (Censorship and the FCC), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 312)
  - Manning, Paul, (Author, Newspaperman, Pulitzer Prize), 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 313)
  - Manning, Paul, (Author, Newspaperman, Pulitzer Prize), 1963-1969 (Box 29, Folder 314)
  - Manning, Paul, (NYC School Decentralization Research: "Time Bomb" A Study of the NYC School Crisis), 1969 (Box 29, Folder 315)
  - Manning, Paul, (NYC School Decentralization Research: "Time Bomb" A Study of the NYC School Crisis), 1969 (Box 29, Folder 316)
  - Maps, (New York State Highway, Airport and Railway), 1961-1966 (Box 30, Folder 317)
  - Matthew, Thomas, (Inter-Faith Hospital), 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 318)
  - Mayors-Big 6, (New York City, Buffalo, Syracuse, Rochester, Yonkers Albany) Budget, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 319)
  - Mayors-Big 6, Budget, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 320)
  - Media, Report of the Governor's Committee on Employment of Minority Groups in the News Media, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 321)
  - Mellor, William, (Proclamations Officer and Writer), 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 322)
  - Messages, Greetings, Miscellaneous, 1960-1963 (Box 30, Folder 323)
  - Messages, Greetings, Miscellaneous, 1964-1968 (Box 30, Folder 324)
  - Messages, Greetings, Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 325)
  - Messages, Greetings, Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 326)
  - Messages, Greetings, Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 327)
  - Messages, Greetings, Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 328)
  - The Mets, (Nelson A. Rockefeller Statement) October, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 329)
  - Migdail, Carl, Latin America and the Rockefeller Foundation, 1970-1972 (Box 31, Folder 330)
  - Mitchell, Bill, Nelson A. Rockefeller Speech Writer, (Business and Finance), 1968-1974 (Box 31, Folder 331)
  - Mitzelle, William, (Hemisphere and Organization of American States Association, Latin American Policies), 1963-1973 (Box 31, Folder 332)
  - Moreland Commission on Nursing Homes, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 333)
  - Moses, Robert, Biographical Information, 1964-1970 (Box 31, Folder 334)
  - Museums, Correspondence, Showing of Nelson A. Rockefeller Art Collections, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 335)
  - "M" Miscellaneous, 1960-1974 (Box 31, Folder 336)
  - Narcotics, Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 337)
  - Narcotics, Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 338)
  - Narcotics, Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 339)
  - Narcotics, Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 340)
  - Narcotics, (Campbell, Rodney) Book Materials, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 341)
  - Narcotics, (Campbell, Rodney) Book Materials, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 342)
  - Narcotics, (Campbell, Rodney) Book Materials, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 343)
  - Narcotics, (Chambers, Carl D. Ph. D.) "An Assessment of Drug Use in the General Population" New York State Narcotic Addition Control Commission, 1971 May (Box 32, Folder 344)
  - Narcotics, Drug Forum, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 345)
  - Narcotics, New York State Drug Abuse Program, New Law, Advertising Campaign, 1973 September (Box 33, Folder 346)
  - Narcotics, New York State Drug Abuse Program, New Law, Advertising Campaign, 1973 September (Box 33, Folder 347)
  - Narcotics, New York State Drug Abuse Program, New Law, Background Data, 1973 September (Box 33, Folder 348)
  - Narcotics, New York State Drug Abuse Program, New Law, Background Data, 1973 September (Box 33, Folder 349)
  - Narcotics, Press Releases, Testimony, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 350)
  - Narcotics, Educational Film by Mayles Brother's, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 351)
  - Narcotics, Finkelstein, Jerry (National Council for Drug Abuse Prevention), 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 352)
  - Narcotics Program (Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 353)
  - Narcotics Program (Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1973 (Box 34, Folder 354)
  - Narcotics Program (Miscellaneous Notes, Background Material), 1973 (Box 34, Folder 355)
  - Narcotics Program (Miscellaneous Notes, Background Material), 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 356)
  - Narcotics Program (Miscellaneous Notes, Background Material), 1966-1970 (Box 34, Folder 357)
  - Narcotics Program (Miscellaneous Notes, Background Material), 1962 (Box 34, Folder 358)
  - National Governor's Conference, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 359)
  - New York City Charter Revision, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 360)
  - New York City Charter Revision, Background Material, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 361)
  - New York City Miscellaneous, (See also John Lindsey), 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 362)
  - New York City Miscellaneous, (See also John Lindsey), 1971 (Box 35, Folder 363)
  - New York City, Nelson A. Rockefeller Statements on City-State Fiscal Crisis, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 364)
  - New York City Scott Commission State Committee to Investigate The City Agencies, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 365)
  - New York City Scott Commission State Committee to Investigate The City Agencies, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 366)
  - New York City Scott Commission State Committee to Investigate The City Agencies, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 367)
  - New York City Statehood, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 368)
  - New York Magazine, (The Case Against Nelson A. Rockefeller), 1970 (Box 35, Folder 369)
  - New York State-City, 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 370)
  - New York State Development Plan, Office of Planning Coordination, 1971 January (Box 36, Folder 371)
  - New York State Department Summaries, Commission Cabinet Reports, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 372)
  - New York State Department Summaries, Commission Cabinet Reports, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 373)
  - New York State Department Summaries, Commission Cabinet Reports, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 374)
  - New York State Department Summaries, Commission Cabinet Reports, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 375)
  - New York State Miscellaneous, 1963-1973 (Box 36, Folder 376)
  - O'Donnell, Harry Admiral, New York State Department of Commerce, 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 377)
  - New York State Salaries (Officials), 1969-1972 (Box 37, Folder 377A)
  - New York State, "A State Can Meet its Responsibilities", 1963 October (Box 37, Folder 378)
  - New York State, "A State Can Meet its Responsibilities", 1962 June (Box 37, Folder 379)
  - Newspapers, Proposal to Start New Paper, (See also Bergenheim, Bob), 1973 March 19 (Box 37, Folder 380)
  - Nixon, Richard Administration, 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 381)
  - Nixon, Richard Administration, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 382)
  - Nixon, Richard Administration, "The Nixon Report", 1968 (Box 37, Folder 383)
  - Nixon, Richard-Rockefeller, Nelson, 1969-1975 (Box 37, Folder 384)
  - Nixon, Richard-Rockefeller, Nelson, Statements Supporting the President, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 385)
  - Nolan, Joseph, Chase Manhattan Senior Vice President, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 386)
  - Noun, Ted, Public Relations and Publicity, 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 387)
  - "N" Miscellaneous, 1961-1971 (Box 37, Folder 388)
  - O'Gara Frank, Architects, 1969-1972 (Box 38, Folder 389)
  - O'Neill, Hester (Free-lance Writer and Editor) Interview Nelson A. Rockefeller on World War II Office of Facts and Figures, 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 390)
  - "Open Skies" Quantico Files at 5600 De-Classification, 1971-1973 (Box 38, Folder 391)
  - Ostrowidzki, Vic, (Political Affairs Editor, Albany Times Union), 1974 (Box 38, Folder 392)
  - "O" Miscellaneous, 1965-1973 (Box 38, Folder 393)
  - Peirce, Neal, (Writer-"The Mega-States of America") Commission on Critical Choices, 1972-1974 (Box 38, Folder 394)
  - Peirce, Neal, (Writer-"The Mega-States of America") Commission on Critical Choices, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 395)
  - Perot, Ross, (Electronic Data Systems Federal Corporation) Miscellaneous Contracts-New York State, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 396)
  - Photographs, Miscellaneous, 1963-1974 (Box 38, Folder 397)
  - Photographs, Photographers, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 398)
  - Photographs, Wand, Bob, 1971-1975 (Box 38, Folder 399)
  - Placek, William, (Speech Writer and Public Relations), 1968-1972 (Box 38, Folder 400)
  - Planning Services, Office of, (Newly Created Office, Five Executive Orders), 1971 (Box 39, Folder 401)
  - Pocantico, New York, National Historic Landmark, Drafts of Isabelle Savell's Manuscript, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 402)
  - Policy Matters, (Clarence Streit), 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 402A)
  - Polls, Miscellaneous, 1970-1974 (Box 39, Folder 403)
  - Polls, Pollsters, (See Also Campaign Files, Polls), 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 404)
  - Polls, Republican Presidential Choice and Political Party Composition, 1973 March-April (Box 39, Folder 405)
  - Polls, Trust and Confidence, 1973 August (Box 39, Folder 406)
  - Politics, Briefing Books for Nelson A. Rockefeller Trips, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 407)
  - Politics, Briefing Books for Nelson A. Rockefeller Trips, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 408)
  - Politics, Lloyd, Free, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 409)
  - Politics, Miscellaneous, 1966-1974 (Box 39, Folder 410)
  - Politics, New York State, (Miscellaneous Party Politics), 1962-1972 (Box 40, Folder 411)
  - Politics, (1976 Election) 1973, 1973-1976 (Box 40, Folder 412)
  - Poverty, (Anti-Poverty Program), 1966 (Box 40, Folder 413)
  - Power and Communication Proposal, (Governor's Conference), 1972 (Box 40, Folder 414)
  - Prospect for America, Front Pages. Tanva Melish Summary, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 415)
  - Public Records, (Availability of), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 416)
  - Public Service Commission, 1969-1972 (Box 40, Folder 417)
  - Public Utilities, (Power Plants, Sites, Equipment), 1968-1971 (Box 40, Folder 418)
  - "P" Miscellaneous, 1961-1973 (Box 40, Folder 419)
  - Racing and Wagering, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 420)
  - Random House, Nelson Rockefeller's Book on the Environment, ("Dear Mr. President"), 1968-1971 (Box 40, Folder 421)
  - Reader's Digest (Manuscript and Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1965-1972 (Box 40, Folder 422)
  - Reader's Digest (Manuscript on Latin America and Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1965-1972 (Box 40, Folder 423)
  - Recreation and Parks, 1960-1971 (Box 40, Folder 424)
  - Redistricting-Reappointment of State Legislature and Congressional Appointments, 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 425)
  - Reid, Ogden, Congressman, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 426)
  - Religion, Blaine Amendment, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 427)
  - Religion, School Prayer, 1962-1964 (Box 41, Folder 428)
  - Republican Governor's Association, (Conference Material), 1973 (Box 41, Folder 429)
  - Republican Governor's Association, (Conference Material), 1971-1973 (Box 41, Folder 430)
  - Republican Governor's Conference, 1973 May 9-11 (Box 41, Folder 431)
  - Republican Party, Miscellaneous, 1959-1973 (Box 41, Folder 432)
  - Republican Party Platform, Miami, Florida, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 433)
  - Republican State Committee, 1970-1974 (Box 41, Folder 434)
  - "A Republican Approach to the Great Issues'" Pamphlet By Nelson Rockefeller, 1960 July (Box 41, Folder 435)
  - "A Republican Approach to the Great Issues" Pamphlet By Nelson Rockefeller, 1960 July (Box 41, Folder 436)
  - Reston, Scotty, (James), New York Times, Washington Bureau, Correspondence on Critical Choices Commission Transcripts, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 437)
  - Revenue Sharing: Article written for the New York Times, never used, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 438)
  - Revenue Sharing: Government Fiscal Crisis in the Federal System, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 439)
  - Revenue Sharing: Government Fiscal Crisis in the Federal System, A Presentation, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 440)
  - Revenue Sharing: Mailing to the Governor's Club (Never Made), 1968-1971 (Box 42, Folder 441)
  - Revenue Sharing: Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 442)
  - Revenue Sharing: Miscellaneous, 1971 December (Box 42, Folder 443)
  - Revenue Sharing: Miscellaneous, 1971 June-November (Box 42, Folder 444)
  - Revenue Sharing: Miscellaneous, 1971 March-May (Box 42, Folder 445)
  - Revenue Sharing: Miscellaneous, 1971 February (Box 43, Folder 446)
  - Revenue Sharing: Miscellaneous, 1971 January-February (Box 43, Folder 447)
  - Richardson, George, (Drug Program), 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 448)
  - Rights: Citizens Rights and Computers, Memo, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 449)
  - Riland, Ken Biography, Nelson A. Rockefeller's Osteopathist, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 450)
  - Robinson, Laymond, Governor's Committee on Minority Groups and Women in Media, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 451)
  - Robinson, Laymond, Governor's Committee on Minority Groups and Women in Media, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 452)
  - Robinson, Laymond, Governor's Committee on Minority Groups and Women in Media, 1970-1972 (Box 43, Folder 453)
  - Rodgers, William H., (Writer, "Rockefeller Follies") Biography, 1966-1971 (Box 43, Folder 454)
  - Romualdi, Serafino (Labor Leader in Latin America, His Memoirs), 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 455)
  - Ronan, William Dr., Biography, (Chairman Metropolitan Transportation Authority), 1973 (Box 43, Folder 456)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Rose Garden Project), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 457)
  - Roper, Burns, (Roper Report) Public Opinion Research Service, 1972-1974 (Box 44, Folder 458)
  - "R" Miscellaneous, 1959-1973 (Box 44, Folder 459)
  - Scandals, Republican Land Speculation Syndicate-Newsday, 1960 February 5 (Box 44, Folder 460)
  - Servicemen, (Veterans, Reservists, etc.), 1961-1970 (Box 44, Folder 462)
  - Sheridan, General Philip H. (Statue in Albany, NY), undated (Box 44, Folder 463)
  - Siller, Raymond, (Humor for Nelson Rockefeller Speeches), 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 464)
  - Simon, Lou, (Off-Track Betting, Job Applicant), 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 465)
  - Simpkins, C. O. Dr. (MESBIC-Community Enterprise Small Business Investment Company), 1972 (Box 44, Folder 466)
  - Smith, Tony, (Ex-Goldwater's Writer-Press Secretary), 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 466A)
  - Speeches: Index by Topic, 1959 September-1961 June (Box 44, Folder 467)
  - Speeches: Index by Group and Organization, 1959 January-1961 April (Box 44, Folder 468)
  - Speeches: Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 44, Folder 469)
  - Speeches: Humorous Material, 1959-1962 (Box 44, Folder 470)
  - Speeches: Speeches printed in pamphlet form, 1960-1963 (Box 45, Folder 471)
  - Speeches Memos to Nelson Rockefeller, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 472)
  - Speeches: Miscellaneous correspondence sent to Morrow from Nelson Rockefeller for possible use in speeches, 1965-1971 (Box 45, Folder 473)
  - Speeches: Speeches written bot not delivered (Medicaid, American Stock Exchange), 1967 September (Box 45, Folder 474)
  - Speeches: Possible useful material on various subjects, (Lincoln, Communism), 1959-1969 (Box 45, Folder 475)
  - Stamps, Commemorative (Requests or Endorsement by Nelson Rockefeller), 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 476)
  - Strikes, Police, 1971 January 15 (Box 45, Folder 477)
  - "S' Miscellaneous, 1962-1974 (Box 45, Folder 478)
  - Taxes, (Sales, Education, State Income Tax, Federal Tax), 1965-1973 (Box 45, Folder 479)
  - Television-Radio, (Invitations to Speak, Cable-TV), 1969-1973 (Box 45, Folder 480)
  - Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1973 (Box 46, Folder 481)
  - Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 482)
  - Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1971 (Box 46, Folder 483)
  - Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1970 (Box 46, Folder 484)
  - Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1968 November-1969 June (Box 46, Folder 485)
  - Television-Radio, (J. Danzig), 1969 July-December (Box 46, Folder 486)
  - Television, David Frost Show, Nelson Rockefeller, 1971 August 5 (Box 46, Folder 487)
  - Television, TV Special on the Executive Mansion, (Homer Poupart), 1968-1971 (Box 46, Folder 488)
  - Television, TV Special on the Executive Mansion, (Homer Poupart, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 488A)
  - Televoice, Governor's Recordings for Radio Use, 1969-1974 (Box 46, Folder 489)
  - Town Meetings, (New York State), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 490)
  - Town Meetings, (New York State), 1969 (Box 46, Folder 491)
  - Trade, Miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 46, Folder 492)
  - Transportation: Highways, 1964-1971 (Box 47, Folder 493)
  - Transportation: Long Island Rail Road, 1969-1973 (Box 47, Folder 494)
  - Transportation: Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 495)
  - Transportation: Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 496)
  - Transportation: Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 497)
  - Transportation: Miscellaneous, 1962-1969 (Box 47, Folder 498)
  - Transportation: Metropolitan Transportation Authority, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 499)
  - Transportation: Metropolitan Transportation Authority, 1968-1970 (Box 47, Folder 500)
  - Transportation: Motor Vehicles, 1971 February-April (Box 47, Folder 501)
  - Transportation: Rye-Oyster Bay Bridge, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 502)
  - Transportation: Traffic Safety, 1962-1973 (Box 47, Folder 503)
  - Transportation: Transportation Bond Issue, 1967-1974 (Box 48, Folder 504)
  - "T" Miscellaneous, 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 505)
  - United Nations Article for Inclusion in U.N. History, (Cancelled), 1965 August 6 (Box 48, Folder 506)
  - Urban Affairs, Office Of, 1966-1972 (Box 48, Folder 507)
  - Urban Crisis, Material, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 508)
  - Urban Crisis, Material, 1960-1965 (Box 48, Folder 509)
  - Urban Development Demonstration Cities (Battery Park), 1967-1970 (Box 48, Folder 510)
  - "U" Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 511)
  - Vasilew, Eugene, Professor of Rhetoric (Politics) Proposed Book of Harper College, 1965-1973 (Box 48, Folder 512)
  - Veterans, (See also Post-Vietnam Planning) New York State, 1970-1973 (Box 48, Folder 513)
  - Veterans, Prisoner's of War, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 514)
  - Veterans, Prisoner's of War, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 515)
  - Vietnam, Miscellaneous, 1964-1970 (Box 49, Folder 516)
  - Vietnam, Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 49, Folder 517)
  - Vietnam, Economics, Post-Vietnam Planning, 1968-1971 (Box 49, Folder 518)
  - Vice Presidency, (See Confirmation Hearings), 1974 (Box 49, Folder 519)
  - "V" Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 49, Folder 520)
  - Walinsky, Adam, (Democratic Candidate for Attorney General Charges Against Rockefeller Administration), 1970 (Box 49, Folder 521)
  - Watergate Statement, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 522)
  - Water Quality, National Commission on, 1973-1977 (Box 49, Folder 523)
  - Welfare, Inspector General, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 524)
  - Welfare, Miscellaneous Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 525)
  - Welfare, Miscellaneous Clippings, Press Releases, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 526)
  - Welfare, Miscellaneous Clippings, Press Releases, 1971 July-December (Box 49, Folder 527)
  - Welfare, Miscellaneous Clippings, Press Releases, 1971 March-June (Box 49, Folder 528)
  - Welfare, Miscellaneous Clippings, Press Releases, 1969 July-1970 December (Box 50, Folder 529)
  - Welfare, Miscellaneous Clippings, Press Releases, 1960-1969 (Box 50, Folder 530)
  - Welfare, Welfare Reform (Medicaid Costs), 1973 July-August (Box 50, Folder 531)
  - Wells, Rich and Greene, (Voter Profile), 1974 April 8 (Box 50, Folder 532)
  - Westchester, New York, Public Relations-Nina Jones, 1970-1974 (Box 50, Folder 533)
  - Westchester, New York, Public Relations-Nina Jones, 1969 September-December (Box 50, Folder 534)
  - Westchester, New York, Public Relations-Nina Jones, 1969 February-April (Box 50, Folder 535)
  - Williams, Roger, (Writer-Book Proposal on Mr. Rockefeller), 1973 (Box 50, Folder 536)
  - Wilson, Malcolm, Governor, 1970-1974 (Box 50, Folder 537)
  - Wolf, Paul, (Trade Specialists to China), 1964-1971 (Box 50, Folder 538)
  - Women, Miscellaneous-New York, 1970-1973 (Box 50, Folder 539)
  - Women, Miscellaneous, New York, 1961-1969 (Box 51, Folder 540)